

IVAN FLORES

323 678 3340 in /Hellolvan 🖂 mzaela@icloud.com

PROFILE

Brand/UI designer based out of Los Angeles, CA. 6 years design experience with 4 years print experience. Know the can and cannot's of print production, an experience not many have. Minimalist aesthetic, and can branch out when necessary. Well spoken with a personality that can deal with a variety of clients. Work ethic is second to none. Determined to do the best of my abilities to ensure a product a client loves. Willing to do what it takes to get urgent projects moving forward to completion.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Sublime Text Illustrator **Photoshop** HTML inDesign CSS JS Acrobat Word Git Mac/Windows Excel **Powerpoint**

PERSONAL SKILLS

Fluent in English and Spanish Works well under pressure Able to adapt to new directions easily Communication is excellent Dedicated to the cause

WORK EXPERIENCE

Production Manager

Gold Image Printing – January 2018 - Present

Specialty jobs moved through me before going into production. In charge of ordering special papers, inks, foils, extra assets, and general preparations for offset, large format, and letterpress jobs. I am a consultant to prepress designers in regards to imposition and file prep. I am the first point of contact when it comes to presschecks and questions regarding clients' orders. I coordinate with pressmen and supervisors to ensure production is on time. I also built relationships with vendors both old and new for whatever would be needed.

Prepress Designer

Gold Image Printing – August 2015 - December 2017

Prepped files before sending to pressmen. Design jobs ranged from logos to cohesive branding packages for clients (business cards, letterheads, labels, etc.) I was the first line when dealing with customers and managed the bulk of orders coming through on our online system and walk-ins.

Designer

Local Print - July 2014 - December 2014

Designed clients' products, which included t-shirts, business stationary, banners, etc. I was first up to service customers. I also typically quoted most projects, which gave me my first taste of business experience.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's of the Arts - Media Arts & Design

Mt. Sierra College – September 2011 - December 2015